Guide to the Duke University Archives Photographic Negative Collection, 1855-1995
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Subject Negatives
  - Subject: Commencements (cont'd) (Box 7)
    - Commencements, honorary degree recipients, 1977 April
    - Commencements, speakers, 1979 May
  - Subject: Concerts
    - Concerts, senior recital, 1956 March
    - Concerts, participants, 1958 March
    - Concerts, participants, 1958 March
    - Concerts, participants, Kay Bowen and Jane Perry, 1958 May
  - Subject: Conferences
    - Conferences, Challenges in Graduate Education, 1963 November
    - Conferences, Graduate School, 1961
    - Conferences, AATS, 1957 October
    - Conferences, above average children, 1963 March
    - Conferences, academic deans, 1961
    - Conferences, admissions, 1961
    - Conferences, admission directors, 1964 February
    - Conferences, AIEE, 1958 May
    - Conferences, AIEE, 1960
    - Conferences, Airpower, 1961
    - Conferences, American Assembly, 1957 June
    - Conferences, American Assembly, 1959 March
    - Conferences, American Assembly, 1959 April
    - Conferences, American Assembly, 1959 April
    - Conferences, American Assembly, 1961
    - Conferences, American Assembly, 1961
    - Conferences, American Assembly, 1964 March
    - Conferences, American Assembly, 1964 March
    - Conferences, American Assembly, 1964 March
    - Conferences, American College Women, 1958 May
    - Conferences, arithmetic, 1959 July
    - Conferences, art, 1963 November
    - Conferences, art institute, 1965 June
    - Conferences, arts festival, 1966 February
    - Conferences, Asian studies group, 1957 September
    - Conferences, Asia, 1962 January
    - Conferences, Asian studies, 1963 September
    - Conferences, bankruptcy, 1963 February
    - Conferences, boarding house, 1958 April
    - Conferences, Boys Club, 1963 May
    - Conferences, BSA, 1960 February
    - Conferences, CEEB and ACAC, 1962 February
    - Conferences, CEEB and ACAC, 1962 February
    - Conferences, Christianity-politics, 1958 June
    - Conferences, church architects, 1964 March
    - Conferences, college-high school relations, 1951 January
    - Conferences, college presidents, 1960 January
    - Conferences, college deans, 1960 January
    - Conferences, communism, 1962 October
    - Conferences, computers, 1964 November
    - Conferences, direct seed symposium, 1959 May
    - Conferences, Durham County Food service, 1965 January
  - Subject: Conferences (cont'd) (Box 8)
    - Conferences, folklore, 1964 April
    - Conferences, food managers, 1964 February
    - Conferences, food service, 1963
    - Conferences, Iceland, 1964 April
    - Conferences, industry, 1961
    - Conferences, international, 1958 November
    - Conferences, international shade tree, 1964 February
    - Conferences, Kappa Delta Pi, 1959 February
    - Conferences, Latin-American conference planning, 1954 February 4
    - Conferences, laundry managers, 1960 January
    - Conferences, lighting, 1956 February
    - Conferences, officers, NC Association of Women Deans and Counselors, 1965 April
    - Conferences, NC College Conference Committee on College Days, 1955 January
    - Conferences, NC English Teachers Association, 1964 July
    - Conferences, NC Religious Council, 1959 February
    - Conferences, personnel, 1949 September 7
    - Conferences, personnel, 1950 September 13
    - Conferences, personnel, 1951 September 10
    - Conferences, personnel, 1952 September
    - Conferences, personnel, 1953 September
    - Conferences, personnel, 1954 September
    - Conferences, personnel, 1957 September
    - Conferences, personnel, 1958 March
    - Conferences, personnel, 1958 May
    - Conferences, personnel, 1959 March
    - Conferences, personnel, 1960 March
    - Conferences, personnel, 1962 April
    - Conferences, Phi Beta Kappa, 1960 April
    - Conferences, physical education, 1960 January
    - Conferences, practical politics, 1966 February
    - Conferences, security, 1965 October
    - Conferences, mayor signing opening of security, 1966 January
    - Conferences, security, 1966 January
    - Conferences, securities regulation, 1964 November
    - Conferences, Hopkins, 1962 November
    - Conferences, Soviet-Chinese conflict, 1964 September
    - Conferences, two challenges, 1962 January
    - Conferences, sewerage groups, 1959 September
    - Conferences, Slavic studies, 1962 October
    - Conferences, South in continuity and change, 1965 February
    - Conferences, SE Accountants, 1962 August
    - Conferences, southeast personnel, 1963 March
    - Conferences, southeastern personnel, 1963 March
    - Conferences, southeastern personnel, 1964 April
    - Conferences, southeastern personnel, 1965 April
    - Conferences, southeastern personnel
    - Conferences, speech association, 1958 January
    - Conferences, Hopkins, 1963
    - Conferences, speakers, 1962 November
    - Conferences, individual in mass society, 1964 November
    - Conferences, tobacco, 1951 October
    - Conferences, tobacco, 1958 October
    - Conferences, US Chamber of Commerce, 1964 March
    - Conferences, Women's symposium, 1963 March
    - Conferences, Superior Student, 1958 November
    - Conferences, World Federalist meeting, 1950 December 4
    - Conferences, commonwealth of children
    - Conferences, speakers on Russia, 1959 December
    - Conferences, health fair, 1964 April
    - Conferences, Chaplains, 1963
    - Conferences, Christian Convocation registration, 1954 June
    - Conferences, Christian Convocation, 1958 July
    - Conferences, Christian Convocation, 1960 February
    - Conferences, Christian Convocation, 1961 October
    - Conferences, Christian Convocation, 1961 October
    - Conferences, Christian Convocation, principals, 1962 August
    - Conferences, Christian Missions, 1956 February
    - Conferences, religious, 1964 April
    - Conferences, Christian, 1960
    - Conferences, Christian, 1961
    - Conferences, Christian, 1961
    - Conferences, Dreschen, speaker at Methodist conference, 1956 August
    - Conferences, Islam, 1963 June
    - Conferences, Methodist laymen, 1958 August
    - Conferences, Methodist men, 1957 July
    - Conferences, Methodist women, 1957 September
    - Conferences, Methodist women, 1958 August
    - Conferences, Methodist women, 1959 August
    - Conferences, Methodist women, 1959 August
    - Conferences, Methodist women, 1959 August
    - Conferences, Methodist women, 1961
    - Conferences, Methodist women, 1961
    - Conferences, Methodist women, 1962 August
    - Conferences, Methodist women, 1963 August
    - Conferences, Methodist youth, 1952 August
    - Conferences, Methodist youth, 1953 August
    - Conferences, Methodist youth, 1953 September
    - Conferences, Methodist youth fellowship dinner, 1954 November
    - Conferences, Methodist youth officers, 1954 August
    - Conferences, Methodist youth, 1954 August
    - Conferences, Unitarian, 1952 November
    - Conferences, Methodist youth, 1961 July
    - Conferences, missions, 1959 February
    - Conferences, mission, 1959 February
    - Conferences, mission emphasis week, 1958 February
  - Subject: Convocation
    - Convocation, annual event, 1964 September
    - Convocation, 1966
    - Convocation, indoor stadium, 1966 September
    - Convocation, 1966 November
    - Convocation, principals, 1966 November
    - Convocation, 1966 November
    - Convocation, 1967 September
    - Convocation, principals, 1967 August
    - Convocation, 1968 September
    - Convocation, Warren Chapman, 1968 September
    - Convocation
    - Convocation, 1971
    - Convocation, Christian, principals, 1970 September
    - Convocation, Christian, 1967 November
    - Convocation, Christian, principals, 1968 September
    - Convocation, Christian, 1969 October
    - Convocation, Grey lecture, Dean Cushman, Father Dickman, 1964 October
  - Subject: Dad's Day
    - Dad's Day, 1950 October 27
    - Dad's Day, poster, 1950 October 27
    - Dad's Day, 1936-1940
    - Dad's Day, 1952 November
    - Dad's Day, annual events, 1953 October
    - Dad's Day, annual event, 1953 October 20
    - Dad's Day, registration, annual event, 1954 November
    - Dad's Day, annual event, 1955
    - Dad's Day, annual event, 1956 November
    - Dad's Day, preparation, annual event, 1957 September
    - Dad's Day, annual event, 1958 November
    - Dad's Day, annual event, 1959
    - Dad's Day, annual event, 1960
    - Dad's Day, annual event, 1961 October
    - Dad's Day, annual event, 1962 November
  - Subject: Debate Team
    - Debate Team, Hart, Knauff, Hauff, April 16
    - Debate Team, 1950 March 10
    - Debate Team, 1955
    - Debate Team, 1955 October
    - Debate Team, 1956 October
    - Debate Team, 1956 April
    - Debate Team, 1957 November
    - Debate Team, 1957 April
    - Debate Team, trip, new volkswagon, 1958 December
    - Debate Team, 1958 April
    - Debate Team, winners, 1954 November
    - Debate Team, 1954 December
    - Debate Team, on trip, 1959
    - Debate Team, girls, 1960 March
    - Debate Team, 1961
    - Debate Team, 1962 January
    - Debate Team, tournament winners, 1962 January
    - Debate Team, Haskell and Patterson, 1963 April
    - Debate Team, trophy, 1964 March
    - Debate Team, 1964 March
    - Debate Team, British, November
    - Debate Team, tournament, 1965 March
  - Subject: Dining Halls
    - Dining Halls, 1950
    - Dining Halls, turkeys in kitchen, 1952 November
    - Dining Halls, Thanksgiving turkeys, kitchen, union, 1954 November
    - Dining Halls, 1962 December
    - Dining Halls, 1963 January
  - Subject: [The] Duke Endowment
    - Duke Endowment, parts of, alumni register, 1957 January
    - Duke Endowment, Rounds and Glasson, oral history, 1963 September
    - Duke Endowment, Rounds visit to Mrs. Williams for university history, 1964 January
    - Duke Endowment, Mr. Rounds and Dr. Spence interview, 1963 May
    - Duke Endowment, Frank Rounds and Mrs. Few interview, 1963 May
  - Subject: Duke Flag
    - Duke Flag, 1963 February
    - Duke Flag, 1963 April
  - Subject: Duke Players [see also Hoof-n-Horn, Box 10]
    - Duke Players
    - Duke Players, laboratory secnes, backstage, identified, 1936-1937
    - Duke Players, house management, 1937
    - Duke Players, five one-act tragedies, 1937 December 9-10
    - Duke Players, "After Dark," 1937 April 29 and May 15
    - Duke Players, "Petticoat Fever," 1937 March 15 and 19
    - Duke Players, "Stage Door," 1938 October 27-28
    - Duke Players, backstage, 1937-1938
    - Duke Players, "Journey's End," identified, 1938 December 15-16
    - Duke Players, "Kind Lady," 1938
    - Duke Players, "Personal Appearance," identified, 1938 May 7
    - Duke Players, Spring Dance, identified, 1939 December 6
    - Duke Players, "Our Town," 1939 October 26-27
    - Duke Players, "Night must Fall," identified, 1939 March 16-17
    - Duke Players, Margin for Error, 1940
    - Duke Players, Winterset, identified, 1940 March 7-8
    - Duke Players, The Drunkard, identified, 1940 May 2 and 4
    - Duke Players, The Torchbearers, 1940
    - Duke Players, Family Portrait, 1940
    - Duke Players, backstage scenes, 1938-1940
    - Duke Players, rehearsal, 1941 March 4
    - Duke Players, Key Largo, identified, 1941 May 1-3
    - Duke Players, Ft. Bragg trip to present "The Male Animal," 1941 November 13
    - Duke Players, "Pinafore," 1942
    - Duke Players, 1943 March
    - Duke Players, "The Ninth Guest," 1944
    - Duke Players, "Ghost Town," 1947
    - Duke Players, 1948 October 29
    - Duke Players, Shadow and Substance, 1948 December 3
    - Duke Players, lab theater, 1948 November 5
    - Duke Players, "Julius Caesar," 1949 March 10
    - Duke Players, "Pygmalian," 1949 April 1
    - Duke Players, 1949
    - Duke Players, 1950 July 11
    - Duke Players, "Arms and the Man," 1951 April 20
    - Duke Players, 1951 October 22
    - Duke Players, 1951
    - Duke Players, "Summer and Smoke," 1952 November 26
    - Duke Players, "Remains to be Seen," 1952 October 22
    - Duke Players, "Uncle Harry," 1952 February 28
    - Duke Players, giving tickets to Mayor Evans, 1953 March
    - Duke Players, Glass Slipper, 1953 February 19
    - Duke Players, laboratory, 1953 December 10
    - Duke Players, adding machine, 1953 November 24
    - Duke Players, 1954 December
    - Duke Players, Time of your Life, 1954 November
    - Duke Players, 1954 October
    - Duke Players, 1954 October
    - Duke Players, 1954 April
    - Duke Players, 1954 March 9
  - Subject: Duke Players (cont'd) (Box 9)
    - Duke Players, "Taming of the Shrew," 1955 March
    - Duke Players, "Man who came to Dinner," 1955
    - Duke Players, "Man who came to Dinner," 1955 November
    - Duke Players, 25th Anniversary, 1955 September
    - Duke Players, "Right you are," 1955 December
    - Duke Players, Merchant of Venice, 1956 March
    - Duke Players, Merchant of Venice, 1956 March
    - Duke Players, 1956
    - Duke Players, 1956 October
    - Duke Players, 1956 November
    - Duke Players, Teahouse of the __ Moon, 1957 October
    - Duke Players, "Misalliance," 1957 March
    - Duke Players, "Volpone," 1958 March
    - Duke Players, "Uncle Vanya," 1958 January
    - Duke Players, "3 Angels," 1958 October
    - Duke Players, 1958 December
    - Duke Players, 1959 November
    - Duke Players, 1959 March
    - Duke Players, Hedda Gabbler, 1959 April
    - Duke Players, "Light up the Sky," 1960 June
    - Duke Players, 1960 May
    - Duke Players, "Death of a Salesman," 1960 March
    - Duke Players, "Death of a Salesman," 1960 March
    - Duke Players, "Crucible," 1960
    - Duke Players, "Macbeth," 1960 April
    - Duke Players, "Born Yesterday," 1961
    - Duke Players, "Born Yesterday," 1961
    - Duke Players, "Tiger at the Gates, 1961 November
    - Duke Players, "St. Joan," 1961
    - Duke Players, "St. Joan," 1961 June
    - Duke Players, "St. Joan," 1961 June
    - Duke Players, "Six characters in search of an author," 1961 December
    - Duke Players, "Skin of our teeth," 1962 March
    - Duke Players, "Skin of our teeth," 1962 March
    - Duke Players, "Skin of our teeth," 1962 May
    - Duke Players, Richard II, 1962 October
    - Duke Players, Richard II, 1962 October
    - Duke Players, "Desire under the elms," 1963 March
    - Duke Players, "Desire under the elms," 1963
    - Duke Players, 1963 October
    - Duke Players, 1964 March
    - Duke Players, 1964 March
    - Duke Players, 1964 March
    - Duke Players, "Bell, book and candle"
    - Duke Players, "Claudia"
    - Duke Players, lab, theater
    - Duke Players, "Boy meets Girl"
    - Duke Players, "My sister Eileen"
    - Duke Players, "The Eve of St. Mark"
    - Duke Players
    - Duke Players, 1968 April
    - Duke Players, 1974 December
    - Duke Players, 1968 May
  - Subject: Duke Press
    - Duke Press, general, 1937-1941
    - Duke Press, publications, 1949 October
    - Duke Press, 1959 March 15
    - Duke Press, story of Durham, 1949 November 22
    - Duke Press, 1953 July
    - Duke Press, feature, 1958 July
    - Duke Press, book on Conrad, 1959 February
    - Duke Press, books, 1957 April
    - Duke Press, Menapace with winning book design, 1962 June
    - Duke Press, Bill Owens and J. Menapace, 1960
    - Duke Press, book winners, 1966 February
  - Subject: Duke University Day
    - Duke University Day, Lake Junaluska, circa 1930
    - Duke University Day, Lake Junaluska, circa 1933
    - Duke University Day, Lake Junaluska, 1934
    - Duke University Day, Lake Junaluska, 1943
    - Duke University Day, 1935 December 11
    - Duke University Day, 1937 December 11
    - Duke University Day, Luncheon and tree planning, 1938 December 10
    - Duke University Day, tree planting, 1939 December 11
    - Duke University Day, senior tree planting, 1943 December 11
    - Duke University Day, tree planting ceremony, 1946 December 11
  - Subject: Durham/Regional
    - Durham/Regional, Holley Hills, 1970 April
    - Durham/Regional, Poplar Apartments, Erwin Rd., Alumni register, 1960 May
    - Durham/Regional, local church organ, 1972
    - Durham/Regional, NC School of the Arts, 1969 November
    - Durham/Regional, Merrick Moore school, project opportunity, 1968 October
    - Durham/Regional, dances, NC School of the Arts, ballet, 1969 November
    - Durham/Regional, Edgemont Youth Center, 1956 October
    - Durham/Regional, Edgemont Youth Center, 1957 October
    - Durham/Regional, Edgemont Youth, 1955
    - Durham/Regional, Edgemont Youth Center, 1956 October
    - Durham/Regional, Edgemont Youth Center, 1956 October
    - Durham/Regional, Edgemont Center, meeting of the board, 1951 May 17
    - Durham/Regional, Edgemont Community Center, planning group, 1951 April 4
    - Durham/Regional, Edgemont Community Center, kids, 1961 August 29
    - Durham/Regional, Edgemont Youth Center, expansion area, 1963 November
    - Durham/Regional, Edgemont Youth Center
  - Subject: Faculty
    - Faculty, advisory group, 1952 September 12
    - Faculty, club, officers, 1963 April
    - Faculty, picnic, 1952 May 17
    - Faculty, club, planning honoring Davison, 1961 September
    - Faculty, club, officers, 1965 April
    - Faculty, club, officers, 1964 April
    - Faculty, club, officers, 1959 January
    - Faculty, club, officers, 1957 April
    - Faculty, club, officers, 1956 April
    - Faculty, club, meeting, 1955
    - Faculty, club, committee
    - Faculty, club, committee for Christmas party, 1961 December
    - Faculty, club, 1959 March
    - Faculty, club, 1958 April
    - Faculty, club, officers with Sen. Erwin, 1955 April
    - Faculty, club, 1953 April 9
    - Faculty, club, 1953 March 12
    - Faculty, club, 1952 October 2
    - Faculty, club, 1952 April 24
    - Faculty, club, 1952 July 10
    - Faculty, club, 1951 October 22
    - Faculty, club, 1951 January 11
    - Faculty, club, meeting, 1950
    - Faculty, outing, 1949 May 28
    - Faculty, club, Edens' first speech, 1949 March 17
    - Faculty, club, 1948 November
    - Faculty, club, Christmas party, 1946 December 17
    - Faculty, club, Dr. Edens, G. Gray, April 24
  - Subject: Flag
    - Flag, raising, first official act of the academic year, 1934-1940
    - Flag, raising, official opening of academic year, identified, 1941 September 17
    - Flag, raising, 1942 September
    - Flag, raising, opening of Woman's Collage, 1945
    - Flag, raising, East Campus, 1946 September 19
    - Flag, raising, West Campus, 1946 September 18
    - Flag, raising, freshman week, East Campus, 1947 September 19
    - Flag, raising, ceremony, West Campus, 1947
    - Flag, raising, 1949 September 9
    - Flag, raising, East and West Campus, 1950 September
    - Flag, raising, East and West Campus, 1951 September 18-19
    - Flag, raising, 1951 September
    - Flag, raising, East and West Campus, 1953 September
    - Flag, raising, 1954 September
    - Flag, raising, officials, East Campus, 1954 September
    - Flag, raising, 1955 September
    - Flag, raising, East Campus, 1955 September
    - Flag, raising, East Campus, 1956 September
    - Flag, raising, East and West Campus, 1956 September
    - Flag, raising, 1957 September
    - Flag, raising, school opening on East Campus, 1957 September
    - Flag, ceremony, East Campus, 1958 September
    - Flag, raising, 1958
    - Flag, raising, West Campus, 1958 September
    - Flag, raising, East Campus, 1959 September
    - Flag, raising, West Campus, 1959 September
    - Flag, raising, West Campus, 1961
    - Flag, raising, 1961 September
    - Flag, raising, 1962 September
    - Flag, raising, 1963 September
    - Flag, raising
    - Flag, lowering, East Campus, class of 1930
  - Subject: Foreign Students
    - Foreign Students, women, 1947
    - Foreign Students, group, 1949 February 24
    - Foreign Students, German, 1950 June 1
    - Foreign Students, German, 1951 July 17
    - Foreign Students, German, 1951
    - Foreign Students, German, 1951 April 24
    - Foreign Students, 1951 June
    - Foreign Students, 1951 September 4
    - Foreign Students, Paramount news, movie of, 1951 October 8
    - Foreign Students, 1952 July 31
    - Foreign Students, 1952 August 22
    - Foreign Students, orientation, 1952 September 4
    - Foreign Students, German, law, 1952 November
    - Foreign Students, French, 1953 May
    - Foreign Students, orientation, 1953
    - Foreign Students, international tea, 1953 October 4
    - Foreign Students, 1953 April 15
    - Foreign Students, India's Independence Day, 1954 August
    - Foreign Students, Pakistan Independence Day, 1954 August
    - Foreign Students, summer school, 1954 August
    - Foreign Students, council, 1954 August
    - Foreign Students, Miss __ at home of Charles Sullivan, summer school, 1955 September
    - Foreign Students, summer school, 1956 August
    - Foreign Students, summer school, 1956 July
    - Foreign Students, group, 1956 August
    - Foreign Students, group, 1957 September
    - Foreign Students, couple, 1957 September
    - Foreign Students, in costume, 1957 September
    - Foreign Students, 1957 September
    - Foreign Students, Pakistan, 1960 February
    - Foreign Students, fractured English group, 1960 February
    - Foreign Students, Christmas feature, 1962 December
    - Foreign Students, South American girl and Christmas tree on East Campus, 1962 December
    - Foreign Students, Vietnamese girl, 1968
  - Subject: Founder's Day
    - Founder's Day, tree planting, 1944 December 11
    - Founder's Day, 1948 December 11
    - Founder's Day, 1949-1950
    - Founder's Day, 1950 November
    - Founder's Day, 1951 December
    - Founder's Day, identified, anniversary, 1951
    - Founder's Day, 1952 December 11
    - Founder's Day, 1953 December
    - Founder's Day, 1954 December
    - Founder's Day, 1955 October
    - Founder's Day, 1955
    - Founder's Day, 1956
    - Founder's Day, 1956 December
    - Founder's Day, Endowment committee and trustees, 1957 January-February
    - Founder's Day, 1957 December
    - Founder's Day, 1958 October
    - Founder's Day, principals, 1959 December
    - Founder's Day, 1959 December
    - Founder's Day, 1961 December
    - Founder's Day, 1961
    - Founder's Day, President Knight, 1963 March
    - Founder's Day, identified, 1964 December
    - Founder's Day, 1966 December
    - Founder's Day, 1964 December
  - Subject: Fraternities/Sororities (Box 10)
    - Fraternities/Sororities, frat house activity, 1954 December
    - Fraternities/Sororities, dream girl, Kappa Sigma, 1958 November
    - Fraternities/Sororities, banquet, Delta Sigma Phi, identified, 1940 April 17
    - Fraternities/Sororities, dinner at Bartlett house, 1953 December
    - Fraternities/Sororities, Beta Power
    - Fraternities/Sororities, fraternity picnic at gate #11, 1957 November
    - Fraternities/Sororities, Pan-Hellenic officers, 1953 March 12
    - Fraternities/Sororities, Pan-Hellenic house, 1953 May 14
    - Fraternities/Sororities, Pan-Hellenic officers, 1954
    - Fraternities/Sororities, Pi Kappa Alpha banquet, 1939 November 25
    - Fraternities/Sororities, Zeta Tau Alpha, 1940-1941
    - Fraternities/Sororities, sorority rushing, 1956 October
    - Fraternities/Sororities, Kappa sorority, 1959 March
    - Fraternities/Sororities, Kappa Alpha Theta, 1953 May
    - Fraternities/Sororities, kids, Christmas, 1966 December
    - Fraternities/Sororities, Sigma Chi, groups with Edens at inauguration, 1949 October 22
    - Fraternities/Sororities, Sigma Chi, sweetheart dance, 1955 February
    - Fraternities/Sororities, Sigma Chi, sweetheart dance and queen, 1956 October
    - Fraternities/Sororities, Pi Kappa Phi, 1987 April
    - Fraternities/Sororities, Kappa Delta Phi, 1961
  - Subject: Freshman/Week
    - Freshman/Week, Woman's College
    - Freshman/Week, 1937
    - Freshman/Week, 1938